toggon.com 2014-04-18

# Toggon.com - Needs sharing social platform - Post free ads on needs related to jobs, services, products and customers

Toggon.com respects the privacy of its users. Toggon.com privacy determines how we treat user information while user visits to our website and uses our services. It is important to us that our user retain their Privacy while pleasing the benefit of the services we offered. 

User/Personal Information

* To avail services on Toggon.com, users are required to provide personal data like Name, Email address, Sex, Date of Birth, Mobile number, Password, Location and Profile Photograph etc wherever required. User availing services on Toggon.com via other social networking websites allows us to obtain information like (User’s Email ID, Contacts, Friends etc) . By accessing our app and giving any information, user gives us permission to use information for business purpose.

Child Protection

* Toggon.com does not offer services to the children who are under the age of 18. If you are below 18 and registered to Toggon.com then we suggest you to delete your account, not doing this would make you solely responsible for all your activities, and its consequences.

Cookies

Depending upon how user is accessing our service, we may use “cookies” or similar technologies to record log data in order to collect information to assign each user a unique identity to understand the individual area of interest.

When user use Toggon.com our web server automatically record limited information about user interaction with our service i.e. “log data”, including the information which browser sends whenever user visit Toggon.com. This log data may include user computer’s connection to the internet, including User internet protocol address, browser type and settings, the date and time of user request. And how user used toggon.com

User Internet protocol address doesn’t identify any user personally; we use this information to deliver our pages to user upon request and to measure traffic within our website.

Confidentiality/Information Security

We have taken some security measures including physical, electronic and other required procedure to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized misuse, modification, discloser, loss and damage of user data we collect online. However Toggon.com doesn’t take any responsibility in case of theft / damage / loss of user’s personal data.

Toggon.com use third party advertising companies to serve ads when any user visits the website. These advertising companies may use relevant information’s may or may not including your name, email address, contact number in order to show advertisements about products, goods and services of respective area of interest to the user.

Third Party Link

Toggon.com doesn’t take any responsibility for the Terms, Privacy Policy or Practices of any third party websites. Users/Advertisers/Promoters should visit third party websites at their own risks.

Toggon.com use third party advertising companies to serve ads when any user visits the website. These advertising companies may use relevant information’s may or may not including your name, email address, contact number in order to show advertisements about products, goods and services of respective area of interest to the user.

Toggon.com has the complete authority to remove third party websites / links if found inappropriate as per the Toggon.com Terms & Conditions defined.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Toggon.com may share user respective information to any third party for business or non-business purpose without obtaining the prior permission of the user. It may include any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of authentication of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.

Ability to Edit or Delete Account Information and preferences

User can improve, correct, modify, edit, and update their information/data by visiting their respective profile page at any time. If any user wants to deactivate its respective account, user has to write us to admin@toggon.com. Our team will deactivate the user account including user all posts, comments, Expressions and other related information from public view. User can activate their account at any stage in future by writing us to admin@toggon.com our team will activate user account and restore all information including all posts, comments, Expressions and other related information.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Toggon.com has the right to Change or amend its Privacy Policy with or without giving any prior notice to users. It is user’s responsibility to read privacy policy regularly and updates.

Contact us

If you have any question related to Privacy Policy of toggon.com, Please write us to: admin@toggon.com   
For any Complain, feedback and Suggestions, please write us to: admin@toggon.com We will appreciate your feedback and suggestions and try to provide you the best service.
